Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXXIV is arranged in 394 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXXIV. WAGES
  - Sub-Series 408-0. Wages
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 20. Hallmann, E.H., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 24)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 21. Hallmann, E.H., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 25)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 22. Behling, B.H., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 26)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 23. "Excerpts From 'Productivity, Prices, and Incomes'", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 27)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 24. Greer, H.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 28)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 25. "The Legal Issues", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 29)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 12. Greer, H.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 30)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 13. Abel, J.F., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 31)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 14. Wolfe, J.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 32)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 15. Wolfe, J.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 33)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 16. Wolfe, J.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 34)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 17. MacGill, W.S., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 35)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 3. "Job Descriptions and Illustrative Examples of Payroll Positions and Duties", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 36)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 2. Watson, Q.D., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 37)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 1. "The Proposals of the Parties and the Appearances for the Carriers", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 38)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Pre-Hearing Brief for the Carriers., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 39)
      1960 April 26
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Post-Hearing Brief for the Carriers., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 40)
      1960 May 28
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Brief for the Eleven Cooperating Railway Labor Organizations., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 41)
      1960 May 29
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 19. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 42)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 18. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 43)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 17. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 44)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 16. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 45)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 19. Hallmann, E.H., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 46)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 18. Hallmann, E.H., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 47)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 11. "Revised Page No. 79 of Exhibit No. 10", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 48)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 9. Monroe, J.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 49)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 10. Symes, J.M., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 50)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 8. Monroe, J.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 51)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 7. Greer, H.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 52)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 6. "Orders, Awards, Agreements, and Reports Relating to the Rates of Pay of Railroad Nonoperating Emplo, 1960 (Box 535, Folder 53)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 5. "Orders, Awards, Agreements, and Reports Relating to the Rates of Pay of Railroad Nonoperating Emplo, 1960 (Box 535, Folder 54)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 4. Greer, H.E., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 55)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 1. "Proposals of Employees and Carrier Counterproposals", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 56)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 3. "Occupational Classification and Number of Non-Operating Employees"., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 57)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 4. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 58)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 5. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 535, Folder 59)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 6. "Examples of Four-Week Vacations, Union Transit Companies, February 1960" (Box 535, Folder 60)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 7. "Paid Holiday Provisions for Industrial Workers", 1960 (Box 535, Folder 61)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 15. Oliver, E.L., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 1)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 25. "The Legal Issues", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 2)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 24. "Excerpts from Testimony, Exhibits, and Briefs Presented by the Organizations to Emergency and Arbi, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 3)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 23. Excerpts from "Productivity, Prices, and Incomes", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 4)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 22. "Productivity: A False Wage Determinant", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 5)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 21. "Employee Demands Presently Confronting the Railroad Industry and Estimated Costs Thereof", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 6)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 20. "Hallmann, E.H., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 7)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 17. MacGill, W.S., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 8)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 16. Wolfe, J.E., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 9)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 15. Wolfe, J.E., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 10)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 14. "Average Straight Time Hourly Earnings of Railroad Employees and Production Workers in Manufacturin, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 11)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 13 (supplement). Abel, J.F., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 12)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 11. "Pennsylvania Railroad: Maintenance Expense Related to Railway Operating Revenues, 1925-1959", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 13)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 9. Monroe, J.E., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 14)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 8. Monroe, J.E., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 15)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 8. "Relevant Features of Hospital, Surgical, and Medical Plans for Industrial Workers", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 16)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 9. "Group Life Insurance in the United States", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 17)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 10. "Productivity of Railway Employees", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 18)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 11. "Real Wages: Health, Education, and Welfare of American Workers", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 19)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 12. "Changes in Earnings, Nonoperating Railway Employees, June 1946-December 1958", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 20)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 13. "Wage Changes: Nonoperating Railway Employees and Employees in Other Industries", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 21)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Employees' Exhibit No. 14. "Railway Financial Position", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 22)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Pre-Hearing Brief for the Carriers., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 23)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Post-Hearing Brief for the Carriers., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 24)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 3. "Job Descriptions and Illustrative Examples of Payroll Positions and Duties", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 25)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 12. "Vacation and Holiday Proposals", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 26)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 18. "Tables and Supporting Material: Recent Wage Agreements in the Railroad Industry", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 27)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 19. "Tables and Supporting Material: Timing of Wage Adjustments", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 28)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 7. "Inter-industry Wage and Earnings Comparisons", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 29)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 4. "Analysis of Inter-industry Wage Progress Comparisons", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 30)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 13. "Material Pertaining to Hospital, Medical, and Surgical Benefits and Group Life Insurance", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 31)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 2. "Railroad Employees and their Compensation Relation of Labor Costs to Revenue Per Unit of Output", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 32)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 10. Symes, J.M., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 33)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 12. "Vacation and Holiday Proposals", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 34)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 13. "Material Pertaining to Hospital, Medical, and Surgical Benefits and Group Life Insurance", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 35)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 14. "Average Straight Time Hourly Earnings of Railroad Employees and Production Workers in Manufacturin, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 36)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 15. "Miscellaneous Materials Relating to Job Content", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 37)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 16. "Job Content and Working Conditions of Nonoperating Employees", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 38)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 17. "Wage Supplements and Related Benefits Applicable to Nonoperating Employees", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 39)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 18. "Tables and Supporting Materials: Recent Wage Agreements in the Railroad Industry", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 40)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 19. "Tables and Supporting Material: Timing of Wage Adjustments", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 41)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 20. "Labor Cost Problem Confronting the Industry", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 42)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 21. "Employee Demands Presently Confronting the Railroad Industry and Estimated Costs Thereof", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 43)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 22. "Productivity: A False Wage Determinant", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 44)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 23. Excerpts from "Productivity, Prices, and Incomes", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 45)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 24. "Excerpts from Testimony, Exhibits, and Briefs Presented by the Organizations to Emergency and Arbi, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 46)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 25. "The Legal Issues", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 47)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 4. "Analysis of Inter-industry Wage Progress Comparisons", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 48)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 5. "Orders, Awards, Agreements, and Reports Relating to the Rates of Pay of Railroad Nonoperating Emplo, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 49)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 6. "Orders, Awards, Agreements, and Reports Relating to the Rates of Pay of Railroad Nonoperating Emplo, 1960 (Box 536, Folder 50)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 7. "Inter-industry Wage and Earnings Comparisons", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 51)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 8. "The Inability of the Railroads to Bear Employment Cost Increases", 1960 (Box 536, Folder 52)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Carriers' Exhibit No. 10. Symes, J.M., 1960 (Box 536, Folder 53)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Proceedings. vols. 1-4, 1960 (Box 537, Folder 1)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Proceedings. vols. 5-9, 1960 (Box 537, Folder 2)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Proceedings. vols. 10-13, 1960 (Box 537, Folder 3)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Proceedings. vols. 14-17, 1960 (Box 537, Folder 4)
    - General. President's Emergency Board. NMB Cases Nos. A-6157 and A-6158. Nonoperating Employees' Wage and Fringe Benefits Case. Proceedings. vols. 18-20, 1960 (Box 537, Folder 5)
    - General. Improvement Factor, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 1)
      January 27, 1953-June 18, 1953.
    - General. Improvement Factor, 1952-1953 (Box 538, Folder 2)
      December 13, 1952-January 25, 1953.
    - General. Improvement Factor, 1952 (Box 538, Folder 3)
      June 1952-December 12, 1952.
    - General. Improvement Factor, 1953 (Box 538, Folder 4-5)
      1953 January 26
    - General. Circulars. 1950 Wage Increase Movement; 1952 Improvement Factor, 1950-1955 (Box 538, Folder 6)
    - General. Improvement Factor. Handbook for Use in National Conferences, 1952 (Box 538, Folder 7)
      1952 December
    - General. Improvement Factor. New York Wage Increase Hearing. Employees' Exhibit No. 2. "National Progress and Rising Real Wages and the Place of Railway Workers in the National Economy", 1953 (Box 538, Folder 8)